Okay,I checked.
我剛看過了
We have Earl Grey,English Breakfast, Cinnamon Stick...
我們有伯爵茶,英式早餐茶,肉桂茶
...Chamomile,Mint Medley, Blackberry and
菊花茶,薄荷茶,黑莓茶
Wait,there's one more. Lemon Soother!
還有…檸檬派
You're not the guy that asked for tea,are you?
你不是那個要喝茶的人對吧?
The One Where The Monkey Gets Away
六人行 第1季 第19集 猴子被送走
-=BT之家DRM小組 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 榮譽出品 河馬根據網絡字幕微調製作
Mail call! Rachel Greene,bunk seven.
瑞秋,你有信
Thank you.
謝謝
Oh,cool! A free sample of coffee.
酷,免費試喝的咖啡
Oh,good. Because where else would we get any?
太好了,因為在哪兒還有免費的咖啡?
Oh,right.
哦,是啊
-Oh,great. -What is it?
-太好了 -那是什麼?
Country club newsletter.
鄉村俱樂部的每日公報
My mother sends me the engagement notices for inspiration.
我媽寄來通知有人要訂婚了
Oh,my God! It's Barry and Mindy!
噢,我的天!是巴瑞和明蒂
Barry,who you almost
巴瑞,你幾乎…
And Mindy,your maid of
明蒂,你的伴娘
Let me see. That's Mindy?
我看看,那是明蒂?
She is pretty!
真漂亮!
Lucky...
她真幸運…
...to have had a friend like you.
有你這樣的朋友
Now it's quiet time.
現在是靜默時間
Marcel,bring me the rice. Come on.
馬修,拿飯給我,快…
Good boy. Give me the rice.
好小子.把飯給我
Thank you. Good boy.
真乖,謝謝
He's mastered the difference between "bring me the" and "pee in the."
他終於能分辨「拿來」和「尿在」的差別了
"Bring me the" and Rach?
瑞秋怎麼啦?
Oh,I'm sorry.
抱歉
This is so stupid!
我真是太笨了
I mean,I gave Barry up,right?
是我不要巴瑞的,對吧?
I should be happy for them.
我應該為他們高興
I am. I'm happy for them.
我…真為他們高興
-Really? -No.
-真的? -不
I guess it would be different if I were with somebody.
如果我和別人在一起就不同了
Whoa,what....
誰,什麼…
What happened to "Forget relationships! I'm done with men!"
你不是說要忘了那段感情,不再和男人在一起
The whole penis embargo?
厭惡男人嗎?
I don't know.
我不知道
It's not about no guys. It's about the right guy.
我想這不是沒有男人的問題, 而是合適男人的問題
With Barry it was safe and easy, but there was no heat.
和巴瑞在一起安全自在 但是沒有激情
With Paolo,all there was,was heat.
和保羅在一起就充滿激情
-lt was this raw,animal,sexual -Right. I got it.
-如野獸般原始的性愛 -好了,我懂
I was there.
我看過你們兩個在一起的樣子
Do you think you can have both?
你認為我能兩者同時擁有嗎?
Someone who's your best friend but also can make your toes curl.
找到一個能當知己 又能讓我感受到激情的人?
Yes.
是呀
Yes,I do. I really do.
我也這麼認為.我真的這麼認為
In fact,it's funny.
其實說來好笑
Often,someone you wouldn't think could...
時常你認為
...curl your toes...
無法讓你感受到激情的人
... might just be the one who...
卻是…
...gets interrupted.
被打斷了
How was the movie?
電影如何?
-Wonderful! -So good!
-很不錯 -很不錯
-Suck fest. -Total chick flick.
-遜斃了 -根本是小妞們看的嘛
I'm sorry it wasn't one of those movies with guns and bombs...
真遺憾這不是槍林彈雨
...and buses going really fast!
公車速度奇快的那種電影
I don't need violence in a movie...
暴力並不能吸引我
...as long as there's a little nudity.
只要有裸體鏡頭我就滿足了
-There was nudity. -I meant female nudity.
-那電影也有裸體鏡頭 -我是指女生的裸體鏡頭
I don't need to see Lou Grant frolicking.
我不愛看盧葛蘭的春宮
Hugh! Hugh Grant!
休葛蘭特!
All right,I've got to go.
我得走了
Come on,Marcel.
走吧,馬修,快
We're gonna go take a bath. Yes,we are,aren't we?
我們去洗澡,對不對?對
They're still just friends,right?
他們只是朋友嗎?
And I will see you tomorrow.
明天見
You're gonna spend tomorrow at Aunt Rachel's.
對,你明天要到瑞秋阿姨家
Does Aunt Monica get a say in this?
等等,摩尼卡阿姨能說句話嗎?
Please,Aunt Monica,please?
摩尼卡阿姨請說?
Unclench. You're not even gonna be here.
別緊張了,你不會在這兒的
-I can't believe we're discussing this. -I agree. I'm,like,in disbelief.
-我無法相信我們竟在討論此事 -我同意,我也無法相信
If it was gonna happen, wouldn't it have happened already?
如果你和瑞秋會愛情產生的話? 還會一直拖到現在嗎?
She said she wants a relationship with someone exactly like me.
她說她在尋找像我這樣的人
She said that?
她真的這樣說?
I added the exactly like me" part.
「像我這樣」是我自己加的
But she's looking for someone. And someone will be there tonight.
她說她在尋找某人,而此人今晚就會出現
"Tonight" tonight?
今天晚上?
It's perfect. It'll just be the two of us.
這樣最好不過了,因為只有我們兩個
She spent all day taking care of my monkey.
她整天都在照顧我的猴子
I can't remember the last time a girl took care of my monkey.
我早已忘記哪個女人照顧過我的猴子
Anyway,I figured after work, I'd pick up some wine...
總之下班後我要去買瓶酒…
...go over there and try to woo her.
去向她「示愛」
Know what you should do?
Know what you should do? 知道你該怎麼做嗎?
Take her back to the 1 890s when that phrase was last used.
帶她回到用「示愛」的十九世紀去
If you keep this up,you'll be finished by the weekend.
如果你繼續這樣,我發誓這星期內 你就可以和這個渾蛋結束
The one in the feathered boa is Dr. Francis.
圍羽毛圍巾的是法博土
Now,she used to be a man.
她曾是個男人
Look,there's Raven.
蕾文出現了
We hate her. We're glad she's dying.
我們討厭她,真高興她就快死了
And then What? Marcel!
什麼?馬修!
Are you playing with Monica's shoes? You're not supposed to
想玩摩妮卡的鞋嗎?你不能玩…
Marcel,did you poo in the shoe?
馬修,你在鞋裡大便?
Oh,Marcel! Bad monkey!
天啊,壞猴子
Oh,God!
哦,天哪!
Sorry,Barry.
抱歉,巴瑞
A little engagement gift.
一份小小的訂婚禮物
I'm sure you didn't register for that.
我相信你沒登記
Who died? Who died?
誰死了?誰死了?
Roll him over! Come on,roll him over!
翻過去!好不好,翻過去!
Well,we know it wasn't Dexter, right,Marcel? Because
好吧,我們知道不是崔斯勒, 因為…馬修?…
Marcel?
馬修?
-How could you lose him? -I don't know!
-你怎會把它弄丟了呢? -天曉得
We were watching TV, he pooped in Monica's shoe....
我正在看電視, 它在摩妮卡的鞋內大便
Wait. He pooped in my shoe? Which one?
它在我的鞋裡大便?哪一雙?
I don't know. The left one!
我不知道,左腳
Which ones?
是哪一雙?
Those little clunky Amish things you think go with everything.
搭配什麼都好看的阿米許鞋
Why is the air in here so negative?
為何一片愁雲慘霧?
Rachel lost Marcel.
瑞秋把馬修弄丟了
Oh,no! How?
不會吧,怎麼丟的?
-He pooped in my shoe. -Which one?
-它在我鞋裡大便 -哪只?
The cute black ones I always wear.
我常穿的那只可愛黑鞋
No,which one?
是哪一隻?
The right or left?
左腳還右腳?
Because the left one is lucky.
因為左腳是幸運鞋
Come on! What am I gonna do?
大家快想辦法!我該怎麼辦?
All right. You're a monkey. You're loose in the city.
有了,如果你是隻猴子,迷失在大城市時
Where do you go?
你會去哪兒?
It's his first time out, so he'll do touristy things.
這是它第一次出門, 所以大概和一般遊客一樣
I'll go to Cats. You go to the Russian Tea Room.
我去百老匯找.你去俄羅斯茶坊
Oh,my God! Come on,you guys!
別再鬧了!
He'll be home any minute. He's gonna kill me!
他馬上就會回家,他不會饒過我的
Search the building. Take the first floor. We'll take the rest.
我們從這棟公寓開始找起 你們找一樓和二樓,菲比和我找三樓和四樓
What am I gonna do?
我該怎麼辦?
You stay here and wait by the phone.
你留在家裡等電話
Spray Lysol in my shoe and wait for Ross to kill you.
在我鞋內嘖芳香劑,順便等羅斯回來殺你
Does anybody want to trade?
有人要交換嗎?
What do you want?
幹嘛?
Mr. Heckles,have you seen a monkey?
哈克先生,我們朋友遺失了一隻猴子 你有看見嗎?
I left a Belgian waffle out here. Did you take it?
我放了威化餅在這兒,是不是你拿了?
-Why'd you leave it in the hall? -I wasn't ready for it.
-你怎會放威化餅在走廊? -我還不想吃
Have you seen a monkey?
你有看見猴子嗎?
I saw Regis Philbin once.
我看過「理吉斯菲邦」
Thank you,Mr. Heckles.
謝謝你,哈克先生
You owe me a waffle.
你們欠我威化餅
He's a black capuchin monkey with a white face...
他是一隻白臉的黑卷尾猴
...with Russian dressing and pickles on the side.
加俄國醬外加醃黃瓜
Thanks.
好,謝謝
How did it go today?
今天過得如何?
Oh,great! It went great. Really great.
很好啊!很好啊.真的很不錯
Is that wine?
那是酒嗎?
You want some?
是的,想喝嗎?
Oh,I would love some.
我非常樂意來點
But let's not drink it here.
可是我們別在這兒喝
I'm feeling crazy. You wanna go to Newark?
我感覺有點瘋狂,我們去紐華克好嗎?
Okay,but before we head off to the murder capital of the Northeast...
前往這東北犯罪首府之前…
... I kind of wanted to run something by you.
…我有些話想說
You know how we were talking before...
我們曾談過…
...about relationships,and stuff.
…感情的問題
-Oh,God,Ross,I cannot do this! -Okay,quick and painful.
-羅斯,我受不了了! -你回絕得倒是很快嘛
Oh,God!
哦,上帝啊!
Okay,all right. All right,okay.
好吧,好吧
Please don't hate me.
羅斯,別恨我
What?
到底是什麼?
You know Marcel?
馬修它…
I kind of lost him.
我把它…弄丟了
I can't believe this.
我真不敢相信
All I asked you to do was keep him in here!
我只是麻煩你別讓它跑出去
I know. I'm sorry.
我知道,對不起
It's partially my fault.
不,我該負一半的責任
I shouldn't have had you start with a monkey.
我不該叫你照顧猴子
You should have started with a pencil.
應該叫你照顧鉛筆才對
I'm doing everything I can. Everyone's looking for him and I got
羅斯,我已盡最大的努力 我已叫大家分頭去找
-Who is it? -Animal Control.
-是誰? -動物控制中心
-I've even got Animal Control. -You called Animal Control?
-瞧,我甚至打給動物控制中心 -你打給動物控制中心?
Why? Do you not like them?
怎麼了?你不喜歡他們?
Marcel is an illegal exotic animal.
馬修是非法的外來動物
I'm not allowed to have him. If they find him,they'll take him away.
我是非法飼養.萬一被他們找到他們就會帶走它
Well,now,see, you never ever told us that.
好吧,可是,你從來就沒有告訴大家
Because I never expected you to invite them to the apartment!
沒錯,因為我沒想到你會請他們來
Thanks for coming.
謝謝你來
Somebody called about a monkey?
有人遺失猴子?
You know,that was a complete misunderstanding.
對,這完全是個誤會
We thought we had a monkey, but we didn't.
我以為我們有養猴子, 但是我們沒有
-Turned out it was a hat. -Cat!
-結果是帽子 -貓!
We checked,no one's seen Marcel.
我們查過了,沒人看到馬修
-My uncle Marcel. -ls that who the monkey's named after?
-我叔叔馬修 -那猴子是以你叔叔命名?
Possession of an illegal exotic is punishable...
你知道持有非法外來動物
... by two years in prison and confiscation of the animal.
可判刑兩年並沒收動物?
Oh,my God!
天啊
You'd put that poor little creature in jail?
你要把這可憐的小東西關進監牢?
Remember how we talked about saying things quietly to yourself first?
菲比,你記得如何先對自己小聲說嗎?
Yes,but there isn't always time.
記得,但總不是時候
I'm sure there's some friendly way to reconcile this. Have a seat.
我相信我們能以友善的處理方式,請坐
We haven't met. I'm Monica Geller.
首先,我們還沒自己介紹,我叫摩妮卡
Oh,my God,you are!
天啊,你是莫尼卡
And you're Rachel Greene!
還有,你是瑞秋對嗎?
Luisa Gianetti! Lincoln High?
露莎,林肯高中
I sat behind you guys in homeroom.
我坐在你們後面
Luisa! Oh,my God!
露莎!哦,天哪!
Monica! It's Luisa!
摩妮卡,是露莎
I went there too!
我也去了那裡!
Luisa! From homeroom!
是在後面那個?
You have no idea who I am,do you?
你們根本不知道我是誰對不?
-No. -Not at all.
-不 -一點也不
Well,maybe that's because you spent four years ignoring me.
或許你們那四年,都在當我不存在
Would it have been hard to say, "Morning,Luisa"...
難道說「早安,露莎」
...or "Nice overalls"?
或「好漂亮的連身褲」有那麼困難嗎?
Oh,I'm so sorry!
對不起
It's not so much you. You were fat. You had your own problems.
我不怪你,你當時很胖, 你有自己的煩惱
But you. What a bitch!
可是你實在是個賤貨
What?
什麼?
You know what? Be that as it may...
別計較了
...could you help us with the monkey thing,for old times'sake?
你真認為你能幫我們找猴子? 看在過去的份上?
Go,Bobcats!
幫我們找
I could. But I won't.
我可以,我不
If I find that monkey,he's mine.
如果我找到猴子,它就是我的了
Sorry.
抱歉
Marcel?
馬修?
Hi,can I help you?
需要幫忙嗎?
We're having an emergency, and we were looking for something.
我們有急事,我們在找東西
-A monkey. -Yes,have you seen any?
-猴子 -對,你有看見嗎?
No,I haven't seen a monkey.
我沒看見猴子
Can you fix radiators?
你知道如何修理散熱器嗎?
Sure! Did you try turning the knob back the other way?
當然!你試過將轉鈕轉回去嗎?
-Of course! -Oh. Then,no.
-當然! -那之後我就不知道了
-Taste this. Is there too much rum? -Just a second.
-試試這個是不是加太多蘭姆酒了? -等等
-Hope you find your monkey. -No,wait!
-希望你們能找到猴子 -不,等等
We may not know about radiators...
我們對散熱器或許不太懂
... but we do have expertise in the heating and cooling milieu.
我們可是冷暖環境的專家
Aren't we in the middle of something?
我們不是正在忙嗎?
But these women are very hot, and they need our help.
對,她們很熱而且需要幫助
And they're very hot!
而且很火辣
We can't,all right?
我們不行
We're sorry.
抱歉你們不知道
You don't know how sorry. We promised to find this monkey.
我們有多抱歉,我們答應人家要找猴子
He's this high and answers to the name Marcel.
它約這麼高,名叫馬修
So if we could get pictures of you, it'd help us out.
如果能擁有你們的照片,就算是幫了大忙
From now on,you don't get to talk to other people.
從現在起不准你和其他人講話
-Oh,my God! -What?
-噢,我的天! -什麼?
Something brushed up against my right leg.
有東西碰到我的右腳
Oh,it's okay. It was just my left leg.
沒什麼,是我的左腳
Look,Phoebe!
看,菲比
Oh,Marcel! Come here!
馬修,過來…
Step aside,ladies.
站過去,兩位小姐
-What are you gonna do? -Just a tranquilizer.
-你要幹什麼? -打鎮定劑
Run,Marcel,run!
快跑,馬修,快跑!
Damn!
壞了!
-Are you okay? -I think so.
-你還好吧? -還行.哦
Oh,gosh!
哦，糟了!
We've been all over the neighborhood! He's just gone!
我們把周圍的鄰居都找遍了, 它不見了,就這麼消失了
-You don't know that. -It's cold,it's dark.
-羅斯,還不一定 -拜託,天氣好冷天又黑
He doesn't know the Village!
它根本不認識路!
And now I have a broken foot. I have no monkey and a broken foot!
現在我的腳又受傷了, 猴子沒了還換來受傷的腳
Thank you very much!
真的感謝你!
I've said I'm sorry a million times.
羅斯,我已向你道歉過無數次
What do you want me to do?
你到底要我怎麼樣?
You want me to break my foot too? I'll break it right now.
你也要我的腳受傷?要我也把腳弄傷
Oh,my God! There,are you happy now?
瞧,高興了吧
Yeah,now that you kicked the sign...
對,你踢完路標後
... I don't miss Marcel anymore!
我突然不再想念馬修了
It's not like I did this on purpose.
我真的不是故意的
No,this is just vintage Rachel.
當然,這是典型的瑞秋
Things just sort of happen around you!
這種事常發生在你身上
You're off in "Rachel Land," doing your "Rachel Thing"...
你活在自己的世界中 做著自己的事情…
...oblivious to people's monkeys or to people's feelings and
完全無視別人的猴子, 或是別人的感覺…
I don't want to hear it! Forget it,okay?
羅斯,我不想聽!忘了他,好不好?
What?
什麼?
Hey,banana man!
嗨,香蕉男!
This is so intense!
這下可好
One side of my butt is totally asleep and the other side has no idea.
一邊的屁股在睡覺, 另一邊卻毫無所知
-What's with Phoebe? -Tranquilizer dart.
-菲比怎麼啦? -麻醉槍
Hi! Did you order some bananas?
你有訂香蕉嗎?
-What about it? -Give me my monkey back!
-那是幹嗎的? -還我的猴子
-I don't have a monkey. -Then what's with the bananas?
-我沒猴子 -幹嘛買一箱香蕉?
Potassium.
補充鉀
Okay,where is he?
馬修?它在哪兒?
You're wasting your time.
你在浪費時間
What?
什麼?
-What have you done to him? -That's my monkey. That's Patty.
-你對他幹了什麼? -這是我的猴子,它叫佩蒂
Are you insane? Come here,Marcel.
你瘋了不成?過來,馬修…
Come here,Patty.
過來,佩蒂
Come here,Marcel.
過來,馬修…
Come here,Patty.
過來,佩蒂
Here,monkey.
猴子過來…
Here,monkey!
過來,猴子!
Gotcha!
總算逮到你了
-Give me my monkey back! -It's mine.
-把我的猴子還給我 -那是我的猴子
Take this up with the judge.
你們到法官面前去爭吧
That's not my monkey. The dress is mine. Send it back whenever.
那不是我的猴子 只有衣服是我的,隨時可以送回來
All right,I want my monkey!
好吧,我要我的猴子!
-Oh,come on,Luisa. -Sorry,prom queen.
-露莎,拜託 -抱歉了,舞會皇后
You had to be a bitch in school, instead of fat.
你高中時幹嘛那麼賤,為何不當個胖妹?
In high school,I was prom queen...
在學校我是舞會皇后
...and the homecoming queen and you...
返校皇后,但是你
...were also there.
你也在的啊
But this isn't high school. We're all adults here!
但是這不是高中,我們現在都是成年人!
Heckles! Can I have this?
我能要這個嗎?
For the most part.
隨意
If you take this monkey,I'll lose an important person in my life.
如果你把猴子帶走 我將失去我生命中重要的人
You can hate me if you want, but please do not punish him.
你可以恨我,請別折磨他
You have a chance to be the bigger person here.
此時你有機會成為大人物
Take it!
把握機會吧
No.
不
All right. Then I'll call your supervisor and tell her...
那麼,我只好告訴你的長官
...you shot my friend with a dart!
你在我朋友的屁股上開了一槍
It'll be nice to get this off, won't it?
終於能脫去這件衣服,不是嗎?
Or we can leave it on. That's fine.
或是這樣也不錯
With the right pumps, that would be a great little outfit.
配上鞋就是完整的一套
Listen,I'm sorry I was so hard on you before
抱歉,我對你這麼凶
No,it was my fault. I almost lost your
不,這都是我的錯,我差點…
Yeah,but you got him back. You were great.
不,它也是你找回來的,你做得很好
We still have that bottle of wine.
那瓶酒還在
Are you in the mood for something grape?
有心情喝杯葡萄酒嗎?
-Sure,that would be good. -All right.
-好呀 -很好
The neighbors must be vacuuming.
隔壁一定在用吸塵器
Well,as long as we're here...
只要我們在這兒…
...and not on the subject....
…不談那個話題…
I was thinking about...
我在想…
... how mad we got at each other before.
…我們剛剛實在是惡言相向
And maybe it was partially because of how we
大概是因為我們…
-Rachel? -Barry?
-瑞秋? -瑞秋?
I can't do it. I can't marry Mindy.
我辦不到.我無法和明蒂結婚
I think I'm still in love with you.
我想我愛的人依然是你
We have got to start locking that door!
我們得開始鎖門了!
Show us! Come on!
給我們看看!來嗎!
-lt was such a long time ago. -Okay,fine. All right.
-很久很久以前 -好吧
This is me in The Sound of Music. See the von Trapp kids?
這是我在「音樂之聲」裡面, 看見范崔普的孩子嗎?
That's because I'm in front of them.
因為我擋在他們前面
Big nun!
大修女!
I thought that was an alp.
我以為那是阿爾卑斯山
High school wasn't my favorite time.
我的高中時代並不如意
I loved high school.
我愛高中
It was four years of parties, dating and sex and
四年的舞會,約會和做愛
Well,I went to boarding school with 400 boys.
我和400個男孩上的住宿學校
Any sex I had would've involved a major lifestyle choice.
每次做愛都是一次生活方式的重大抉擇
Doesn't it seem like a million years ago?
天啊,那不是回到史前時代?
My butt cheek is waking up!
我的屁股醒了